// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
      question: "Is a popular literary device in which the repetition of the same or similar sounds occur in two or more words",
      answer: "Rhyme",
      options: [
        "Synonyms",
        "Antonyms",
        "Rhyme",
        "Same",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
      question: "Is the pattern of rhyme at the end of each verse or line in poetry",
      answer: "Rhyme scheme",
      options: [
        "Rhyme scheme",
        "Pyramid scheme",
        "Financial scheme",
        "Hybrid scheme",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
      question: "These are the common rhyme scheme Except:",
      answer: "Perfect rhyme",
      options: [
        "Ballade",
        "Perfect rhyme",
        "Couplet",
        "Alternate",
      ]
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
      question: "This type of rhyme scheme uses ABBA rhyme",
      answer: "Enclosed rhyme",
      options: [
        "Triplet",
        "Enclosed rhyme",
        "Couplet",
        "Monorhyme",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
      question: "This type of rhyme scheme uses specific rhyme scheme as ABABCDECDE",
      answer: "Keats odes",
      options: [
        "Keats odes",
        "Terza rima",
        "Limerick",
        "Villanelle",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
      question: "This type of rhyme scheme uses tercets or 3-line stanza such as ABA, BCB, CDC, DED, etc",
      answer: "Terza rim",
      options: [
        "Triplet",
        "Keats odes",
        "Quatrain",
        "Terza rima",
    ]
  },
{
    numb: 7,
      question: "This type of rhyme scheme uses use five lines as AABBA",
      answer: "Limerick",
      options: [
        "Villanelle",
        "Quatrain",
        "Enclosed rhyme",
        "Limerick",
      ]
  },
{
    numb: 8,
      question: " This type of rhyme scheme is a 19-line poem consisting of 5 tercets and final quatrain",
      answer: "Villanelle",
      options: [
        "Limerick",
        "Keats odes",
        "Villanelle",
        "Terza rima",
      ]
  },
{
      numb: 9,
      question: "This type of rhyme scheme also known as AB AB rhyme scheme. It rhymes as ABAB CDCD EFEF GHGH",
      answer: "Alternate",
      options: [
        "Balade",
        "Alternate",
        "Monorhyme",
        "Quatrain",
      ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
      question: "This type of rhyme scheme contains three (3) stanzas with rhyme scheme of ABAB BCBC",
      answer: "Ballade",
      options: [
        "Ballade",
        "Limerick",
        "Enclosed rhyme",
        "Triplet",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 11,
      question: "This type of rhyme scheme uses the same rhyme scheme in every line",
      answer: "Monorhyme",
      options: [
        "Monorhyme",
        "Ballade",
        "Alternate",
        "Couplet",
    ]
  },
{
    numb: 12,
      question: "This type of rhyme scheme is a two-line stanza rhyme scheme which may also be AA, BB, CC, DD",
      answer: "Couplet",
      options: [
        "Villanelle",
        "Limerick",
        "Couplet",
        "Triplet",
    ]
  },

{
    numb: 13,
      question: "This type of rhyme scheme often repeats like couplet which uses AAA rhyme scheme",
      answer: "Triplet",
      options: [
        "Terza rima",
        "Couplet",
        "Ballade",
        "Triplet",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 14,
      question: "This type of rhyme scheme uses A1bA2, abA1, abA2, abA1, abA2, abA1A2",
      answer: "Quatrain",
      options: [
        "Quatrain",
        "Alternate",
        "Ballade",
        "Couplet",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 15,
      question: "What type of rhyme scheme is given: Hakuna Matata, What a wonderful phrase, Hakuna Matata, Ainâ€™t no passing craze",
      answer: "Must",
      options: [
        "Should",
        "Must",
        "Can",
        "Shouldn't",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 16,
      question: "What is this sentence express? you should validate someones opinion",
      answer: "Obligation",
      options: [
        "Obligation",
        "Possibility",
        "Permission",
        "Prohibition",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 17,
      question: "What is this sentence express? we cant just let them die",
      answer: "Prohibition",
      options: [
        "Obligation",
        "Possibility",
        "Permission",
        "Prohibition",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 18,
      question: "What is this sentence express? can I take this?",
      answer: "Permission",
      options: [
        "Obligation",
        "Possibility",
        "Permission",
        "Prohibition",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 19,
      question: "What is this sentence express? since its already evening, can we stay here overnight?",
      answer: "Permission",
      options: [
        "Obligation",
        "Possibility",
        "Permission",
        "Prohibition",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 20,
      question: "What is this sentence express? we shouldn't hurt someone",
      answer: "Prohibition",
      options: [
        "Obligation",
        "Possibility",
        "Permission",
        "Prohibition",
    ]
  },


  // you can make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];